in this tutorial series will be using
在本系列教程中 我们将使用
audacity the free audio recording and
Audacity免费录音和
editing software and I'm going to be
编辑软件 我将成为
showing you how to use it kind of
向你展示如何使用它
exploring the interface a little bit and
稍微探索一下界面 然后
showing you some different things you
向你展示一些不同的东西
can do with it so it should be a fun
可以用它 所以应该是一件有趣的事情
tutorial series and I'm glad you found
系列教程 我很高兴你找到了
it if you don't already have audacity
如果你还没有胆量的话
installed you can check out my other
安装后 您可以查看我的其他
video it is legitimately free
视频是合法免费的
open-source software you can download
您可以下载的开源软件
and use it it's not a free trial version
并使用它 它不是免费试用版
or there's no tricks involved this is
否则就不会有什么诡计这是
just great free software that you can
只是你能做到的很棒的自由软件
use to create podcasts to record
用于创建要录制的播客
instruments interviews I'm using it to
我正在用它来进行采访
do my tutorial videos to record the
制作我的教程视频来录制
audio for some of my tutorials it's just
我的一些教程的音频只是
great free software and it's
伟大的自由软件和它的
full-featured so go ahead and get that
功能齐全 所以请继续并获得
downloaded installed and then come back
已下载安装 然后返回
to these tutorials I'm using it on
对于这些教程 我正在使用它
Windows 10 it works on Linux and Mac as
Windows 10它可以在Linux和Mac上运行
well the first thing you want to do when
嗯 你想做的第一件事是
it's first installed is to go ahead and
它的第一个安装是继续进行和
just try and do a test recording just
只是试着做一段测试录音
right out the gate hit this record
就在大门外 创造了这个纪录
button and then when you're done hit the
按钮 然后在完成后点击
stop button so I'm just gonna do that
停止按钮 所以我要这么做
this is a test audio recording and then
这是一段测试录音 然后
we just hit play this is a test audio
我们刚刚点击了播放这是一个测试音频
recording so the fact that we can play
录制 这样我们就可以播放
that back and listen to it the fact that
回到过去 听一听这个事实
we see these blue waveforms appear down
我们看到下面这些蓝色的波形
here tells me that my microphone is
这里告诉我 我的麦克风
working and that my speakers are working
我的扬声器也在工作
so if you hit record and you just have a
所以 如果你创了纪录 你只有一个
solid blue line and you don't see any
实心的蓝线 你看不到
activity even when you're talking that's
即使当你说话的时候 你的活动也是
just saying that audacity doesn't know
我只是说 厚颜无耻的人不知道
what input device to use it doesn't it's
用什么输入设备 不是吗？
not or it doesn't the input device
不是或不是输入设备
you've told it to use isn't working
你告诉它使用它是不起作用的
properly that could mean you might have
正确地说 这可能意味着你可能有
a switch on your a lot of times a
打开你的开关很多次A
headset with a built-in microphone will
带有内置麦克风的耳机将
have a switch that you can turn on and
有一个开关 你可以打开它
off to toggle if your microphones on or
关闭以在您的麦克风打开或打开时切换
off obviously your microphone has to be
显然你的麦克风必须关掉
plugged into your computer if you want
如果您需要 可以插入您的计算机
to use the webcam microphone that's
要使用网络摄像头麦克风
built into like a laptop you specify all
就像一台笔记本电脑一样内置 你可以指定所有
that and to do that if we hover over
如果我们将鼠标悬停在
here and look we see we have a
在这里 我们看到我们有一个
microphone symbol and a speaker symbol
麦克风符号和扬声器符号
and we can actually change what we're
我们实际上可以改变我们的现状
using as our default device so I was
使用作为我们的默认设备 所以我
recording using my rode microphone my
使用我的骑行麦克风录制我的
USB mic but if I were to use this which
USB麦克风 但如果我用这个
is my webcam my HD webcam HD pro webcam
我的摄像头是我的高清摄像头高清专业摄像头吗
I can actually come here to the
我真的可以来这里
this recording and hit record again this
这张唱片又打了这张唱片
is a test audio recording and we see the
是一个测试录音 我们可以看到
wave looks different and it's gonna
波浪看起来不一样了 它会
sound a lot different too if we play
如果我们演奏 听起来也会有很大的不同
back one is using my rode microphone and
后面的人在用我的RADE麦克风
one is using my webcam microphone this
其中一个用的是我的网络摄像头麦克风
is a test audio recording recording so
测试录音是这样录制的吗
you can change the input that you're
您可以更改正在进行的输入
using on this tab if you use this
如果使用此选项卡 请在此选项卡上使用
Microsoft sound mapper that basically
微软的声音映射器基本上
just means if I right-click down here
我的意思是 如果我在这里右击
and go to open sound settings that
并转到打开声音设置
basically means whatever you're telling
基本上就是说无论你在说什么
Windows to use as your default device
用作默认设备的Windows
use that so my default device is my rode
使用它 这样我的默认设备就是我的Rode
microphone so using Microsoft sound
使用Microsoft Sound的麦克风
mapper and using my rode microphone
Mapper和使用我的RADE麦克风
option are gonna have the same result so
选项会有相同的结果 所以
over here under speakers it has the same
在这里的扬声器下面 它有相同的
option we can say use Microsoft sound
我们可以说使用Microsoft Sound
mapper so whatever your your control
映射器 所以无论你控制什么
panel settings are set up for - for your
面板设置是为-为您的
audio that's just what it'll it'll do so
音频 这就是它会做的 它会这样做
that's that might be your best option
那可能是你最好的选择
try that at first there's a couple
先试试看 有几个
different ways to configure it but I'm
不同的方式来配置它 但是我
using my speakers and headphones as my
使用我的扬声器和耳机作为我的
playback device it's just my real tech
回放设备 这是我真正的技术
built-in audio interface that's built
内置音频接口
into the computer I have an option also
在电脑里我也有一个选项
to use my rode microphone as an output
使用我的RADE麦克风作为输出
device because my microphone has a
因为我的麦克风有一个
headphone jack on it that I could use
上面有耳机插孔 我可以用
but I don't have any headphones plugged
但是我没有插任何耳机
in right now and so if I try and play
如果我试着打球 现在就开始
this it's playing but I'm not hearing
它在播放 但我听不到
the audio that's because I'm using the
音频那是因为我用的是
wrong output device or I'm using an
错误的输出设备或我使用的是
output device that doesn't have anything
没有任何内容的输出设备
plugged into it right now so just play
现在就接通了 所以就玩吧
around with those to get your right
和那些人在一起 以获得你的权利
configuration to actually record and
配置为实际录制和
hear something another way to get in to
听到另一种进入的方式
looking at these is to go to edit and go
看这些就是去编辑 然后去
down to preferences and then the first
向下到偏好 然后是第一个
tab here is devices and you can change
这里的标签是设备 您可以更改
it here it's the exact same options it's
它在这里 它是完全相同的选择 它
just a different way to look at it and
只是用不同的方式来看待它
it gives you a little bit more options
它为您提供了更多的选择
as far as you can change this host so
只要您可以将此主机更改为
you might need to change that but I'm
你可能需要改变这一点 但我
just leaving mine mine hadn't happened
只是离开我的我的并没有发生
to work and this is some of these
去工作 这是其中的一部分
options are gonna look different for you
对于你来说 选择会有所不同
you're not gonna have rode microphone
你不会骑着麦克风
unless you have a rode microphone
除非你有骑马麦克风
plugged in yours might be you know
插上你的可能是你知道的
whatever manufacturer of microphone
无论是什么麦克风制造商
you're using the name of your speakers
你在用你的演讲者的名字
and microphones will be different than
麦克风将不同于
mine but just know that sometimes you
我的但你要知道有时候你
have to play with those to get it to
必须玩这些才能把它带到
work properly
正常工作
that's the extent of x-ray this tutorial
这就是本教程中的x射线范围
I'm just going to show you and in the
我要向你们展示的是
next one we'll actually learn how to do
下一节我们将真正学习如何做
some more with this we'll learn more
有了这个 我们将学到更多
about what this interface is and what's
关于这个界面是什么 什么是
going on but I appreciate you watching
继续 但我很感谢你的收看
this video I hope it's helped to get
我希望这段视频能帮助我
your configure your audio audacity
您配置您的音频放大率
configured properly and in the next
正确配置并在下一页中
video we'll start learning how to record
我们将开始学习如何录制视频
audio and edit audio thanks for watching
音频和编辑音频感谢收看